Herbert Halpert collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Herbert Halpert's fieldwork
  - Subseries 8: Photographic materials
    - Photographic negatives (Box 80)
      - Inside Herbert Halpert's home, probably NY, 19 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
        Includes images inside the house, photos of Halpert and of an unidentified woman, the workplace/library, and an image of a painting by Bruegel the Elder ("The Hunters in the Snow").
      - Unidentified woman, at Halpert's home, possibly in NY, 4 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Herbert Halpert, at Halpert's home, possibly in NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified woman, at Halpert's home, possibly in NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 35 mm
      - Herbert Halpert, at Halpert's home, possibly in NY, 4 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified woman, at Halpert's home, possibly in NY, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Reproduction of the painting "The Hunters in the Snow," by Pieter Bruegel the Elder, at Halpert's home, possibly in NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 35 mm
      - Workplace, library,, at Halpert's home, possibly in NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 35 mm
      - An unidentified man outside a building, probably NY (perhaps northern; i.e., The Catskills), 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified people outside a building (possibly personal friends of Halpert), probably NY (perhaps northern; i.e., The Catskills), 5 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man outside a building, probably NY (perhaps northern; i.e., The Catskills), 4 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man wearing a hat and sitting on a wagon, probably NY (perhaps northern; i.e., The Catskills), 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man (in one image with a pipe), probably NY (perhaps northern; i.e., The Catskills), 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man, seated, indoors in a room with a checkerboard tile floor, probably NY (perhaps northern; i.e., The Catskills), 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man standing on a porch, probably NY (perhaps northern; i.e., The Catskills), 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Two unidentified men standing on a porch, probably NY (perhaps northern; i.e., The Catskills), 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 35 mm
      - Swartwout brothers George and James, East Branch, NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Landscapes, NJ, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Landscapes, including charcoal burning, NJ, 7 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified individuals, probably PA or NY, 8 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm or smaller
      - Woman seated in chair; from a Southern states trip, 1939, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm or smaller
    - Kentucky - contact prints, 1939 (Box-folder 78/10)
      From Halpert's Southern States trip
      - Unidentified man, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 5 in. or smaller
        See afc2004008_halpert-south-KY-pho-contact-prints.pdf for further details.
    - Kentucky - photograph enlargements, 1939 (Box-folder 78/11)
      - Unidentified man, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; approximately 8 in. x 8 in. or smaller
        See afc2004008_halpert-south-KY-pho-enlargements.pdf for further details.
    - Mississippi - contact prints, 1939 (Box-folder 78/12)
      - Unidentified people, some holding musical instruments, 29 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
        See afc2004008_halpert-south-MS-pho-contact-prints.pdf for further details.
    - Mississippi - photograph enlargements, 1939 (Box-folder 78/13)
      - Cap'n Bailey, and other, unidentified people, 9 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
        Two photos of different men are both identified as Cap'n Bailey. See afc2004008_halpert-south-MS-pho-enlargements.pdf for further details.
    - North Carolina - contact prints, 1939 (Box-folder 79/1)
      Photographed in Rominger, NC. From Halpert's Southern States trip.
      - Nathan Hicks, holding a dulcimer, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; approximately 3 in. x 3 in. or smaller
        See afc2004008_halpert-south-NC-pho-contact-prints.pdf for further details.
      - Nathan Hicks, with a woman and child, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; approximately 3 in. x 3 in. or smaller
    - North Carolina - photograph enlargments, 1939 (Box-folder 79/2)
      - Nathan Hicks, holding a dulcimer, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; approximately 8 1/2 in. x 8 in. or smaller
        See afc2004008_halpert-south-NC-pho-enlargements.pdf for further details.
      - Nathan Hicks, with a woman and child, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; approximately 8 in. x 8 in. or smaller
    - Tennessee - contact prints, 1939 (Box-folder 79/3)
      - Unidentified individuals, 32 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 in. x 3 in. or smaller
        See afc2004008_halpert-south-TN-pho-contact-prints.pdf for further details.
    - Tennessee - photograph enlargements, 1939 (Box-folder 79/4)
      - Unidentified individuals; includes photos of Austin Harmon's children, 14 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 8 in. or smaller
        Includes four children identified as Austin Harmon's children, as well as several men and two men. See afc2004008_halpert-south-TN-pho-enlargements.pdf for further details.
    - Virginia - contact prints, 1939 (Box-folder 79/5)
      - Unidentified man, 3 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 in. x 3 in. or smaller
        See afc2004008_halpert-south-VA-pho-contact-prints.pdf for further details.
      - Unidentified woman wearing a cap, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Miss Anne Bell, Richmond, VA, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in.
    - Virginia - photograph enlargements, 1939 (Box-folder 79/6)
      - Unidentified man, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; approximately 8 in. x 6 in.
      - Unidentified woman wearing a cap, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
    - Photographs without IDs, group 1, 1939 (Box-folder 79/7)
      - Unidentified individuals and locations, 19 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 5 in. or smaller
    - Photographs without IDs, group 2, 1939 (Box-folder 79/8)
      - Unidentified individuals and locations, 20 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 5 in. or smaller
    - Photographs without IDs, group 3, 1939 (Box-folder 79/9)
      - Unidentified individuals and locations, 17 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
    - Photographs without IDs, group 4, 1939 (Box-folder 79/10)
      - Unidentified woman, 5 photographs: contact prints, black and white; approximately 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
        The images were delivered to AFC as part of a set identified as part of Halperts 1939 Southern fieldwork. However two negatives of the woman (seated in a chair) were delivered to AFC identified as part of Halpert's fieldwork in NJ, NY, and PA, and in an envelope with other images believed to have been taken in PA.
    - Herbert Halpert, at Halpert's home, possibly in NY, 1939 (Box-folder 79/11)
      - Unidentified individuals and locations, 12 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
        These images were delivered to AFC as part of the Southern field trip. Aspects of the subject matter are not self-evidently "southern" and additional verification is needed.
    - Photograph enlargements without IDs, group 1, 1939 (Box-folder 79/12)
      - Unidentified individuals and locations, 15 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 8 in. or smaller
    - Photograph enlargements without IDs, group 2, 1939 (Box-folder 79/13)
      - Unidentified individuals and locations, 13 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 1/2 in. x 8 in. or smaller
    - Photolab processing envelopes, 1938, 23 paper envelopes. Not all years within the date range are represented by the materials. Halpert's pencilled notations appear on all the envelopes. (Box-folder 79/14)
    - Handwritten note from Violetta Halpert (1/2), 1938, A handwritten note regarding small photographs from the Southern states trip, noting that the majority are from Tennessee and Virginia. The photolab processing envelope is also in the folder. (Box-folder 79/15)
    - Handwritten note from Violetta Halpert (2/2), 1938, A handwritten note about some photo enlargements from Southern states trip. It is presumed this note accompanied materials that are part of the collection. Also in the folder is a cut-out section of an original folder (received thus) with Herbert Halpert's handwritten notes. (Box-folder 79/16)
  - Subseries 8: Sound recordings
    - Sub-suberies 1: Kentucky accrual, AFC staff note: According to Michael Taft, SR001-SR016 are probably original discs.
      Received in 2004. All informants except George R. Lassiter were students at Murray State College.
      - Mary Stites; Jane Earl Johnson, May 26, 1950, AFC 2004/008: SR001; IDB 44324; 27; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mildred Parsons/Reva Lawson/Thelma Lynn Lamkin, May 26, 1950, AFC 2004/008: SR002; IDB 44325; 28; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Martha Dell Sanders, May 15, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR003; IDB 44326; 1/2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Martha Dell Sanders, May 15, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR004; IDB 44327; 3/4; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Jones record duplicate, undated, AFC 2004/008: SR005; IDB 44328; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Jones record, undated, AFC 2004/008: SR006; IDB 44329; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, undated, AFC 2004/008: SR007; IDB 44330; 1/2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, undated, AFC 2004/008: SR008; IDB 44331; 3; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Series A: George R. Lassiter, September 12, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR009; IDB 44332; 1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        George R. Lassiter is not listed elsewhere in this collection.
      - Series A: George R. Lassiter, September 12, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR010; IDB 44333; 2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        See the note for SR009.
      - Series A: George R. Lassiter, September 12, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR011; IDB 44334; 3; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Series A: George R. Lassiter, September 12, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR012; IDB 44335; 4; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Series B: Mrs. R. L. Asher, September 11, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR013; IDB 44336; 1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Series B: Mrs. R. L. Asher, September 11, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR014; IDB 44337; 2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Series B: Mrs. R. L. Asher, September 11, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR015; IDB 44338; 3; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Series B: Mrs. R. L. Asher, September 11, 1951, AFC 2004/008: SR016; IDB 44339; 4; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
    - Sub-suberies 2: Library of Congress dubs of Southern trip records
      Copied from discs in the Herbert Halpert 1939 Southern States recording expedition (AFC 1939/005).
      - Samuel Harmon; Joe Hubbard, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR261; IDB 44774; 1A-1B; AFS 02805 B/AFS 02825 B1-B2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon; Marietta Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR262; IDB 44775; 2A-2B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        Documentation indicates the recording should include "Jack and the beanstalk"
      - Samuel Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR263; IDB 44776; 3A-3B; AFS 02921 A1/AFS 02921 B1-B2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR264; IDB 44777; 4A-4B; AFS 02922 A1-A2/AFS 02922 B1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR265; IDB 44778; 5A-5B; AFS 02923 B2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        Documentation indicates the recording should include "Two young men and their travels," parts 1 and 2
      - Samuel Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR266; IDB 44779; 6A-6B; AFS 02924 A1/AFS 02924 B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR267; IDB 44780; 7A-7B; AFS 02925 A1-A2/AFS 02925 B1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon; Alberta Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR268; IDB 44781; 8A-8B; AFS 02926 A1-A2/AFS 02926 B1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon; Alberta Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR269; IDB 44782; 9A-9B; AFS 02927 A1/AFS 02927 B3; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR270; IDB 44783; 10A-A0B; AFS 02928 A1/AFS 02928 B1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR271; IDB 44784; 11A-11B; AFS 02929 A1-A2/AFS 02929 B1-B2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Samuel Harmon; Marietta Harmon, 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR272; IDB 44785; 12A-12B; AFS 02930 A1/AFS 02930 B1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - seven children [otherwise unidentified], 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR273; IDB 44786; 13A-13B; AFS 03099 A/AFS 03099 B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Informations: two girls; eight children [otherwise unidentified], 1939, AFC 2004/008: SR274; IDB 44787; 14A-14B; AFS 03100 A/AFS 03100 B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
    - Sub-subseries 3: Library of Congress dubs of The Southern Harmony Singers, 1948-1949
      Copied from the Herbert Halpert collection of Kentucky folk music (AFC 1950/005), AFS 09760-09764. Michael Taft added the range of AFS numbers for these discs.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR296; IDB 44809; 22A-22B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR297; IDB 44810; 23A-23B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR298; IDB 44811; 24A-24B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR299; IDB 44812; 25A-25B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR300; IDB 44813; 26A-26B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR301; IDB 44814; 27A-27B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR302; IDB 44815; 28A-28B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR303; IDB 44816; 29A-29B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR304; IDB 44817; 30A-30B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR305; IDB 44818; 31A-31B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR306; IDB 44819; 32A-32B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR307; IDB 44820; 33A-33B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR308; IDB 44821; 34A-34B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR309; IDB 44822; 35A-35B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
    - Sub-subseries 4: Morner Bowden, 1949
      Copied from the Herbert Halpert collection of Kentucky folk music (AFC 1950/005), AFS 09750-09759. According to a note from Violetta Halpert: "Records from Morner Bowden, songs, etc, my baby nurse when Nick was born."
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR286; IDB 44799; 12A-12B; AFS 09750; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR287; IDB 44800; 13A-13B; AFS 09751; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR288; IDB 44801; 14A-14B; AFS 09752; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR289; IDB 44802; 15A-15B; AFS 09753; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR290; IDB 44803; 16A-16B; AFS 09754; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR291; IDB 44804; 17A-17B; AFS 09755; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR292; IDB 44805; 18A-18B; AFS 09756; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        Violetta M. Halpert sings "Shoveling Iron Ore" on AFS 09756 A1.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR293; IDB 44806; 19A-19B; AFS 09757; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR294; IDB 44807; 20A-20B; AFS 09758; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - no available information, AFC 2004/008: SR295; IDB 44808; 21A-21B; AFS 09759; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
    - Sub-subseries 5: Kentucky/Tennessee field recordings
      Copied from the Herbert Halpert collection of Kentucky folk music (AFC 1950/005).
      - Anna French (AFS 09739), April 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR275; IDB 44788; W1; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mrs. Prudie Tillman; Mrs. Nonnie Shanklin (AFS 09740), April 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR276; IDB 44789; W2; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mrs. Prudie Tillman (AFS 09741), April 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR277; IDB 44790; W3; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mrs. Prudie Tillman (AFS 09742), April 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR278; IDB 44791; W4; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mrs. Nonnie Shanklin; Mrs. Prudie Tillman (AFS 09743), April 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR279; IDB 44792; W5; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mrs. Nonnie Shanklin; Mrs. Prudie Tillman (AFS 09744), April 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR280; IDB 44793; W6; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Mrs. Nonnie Shanklin (AFS 09745), April 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR281; IDB 44794; W7; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
      - Harold McLean [Herman R. McLean?] (AFS 09746), October 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR282; IDB 44795; 8A-8B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        A student at Murray State College, whose name appears elsewhere in this collection.
      - Barkley Jones [Thomas Barkely Jones?], Mary Lou Simmons [Mary Louise Simons?], Jean Davis, Miss Jean Erwin (AFS 09747), September 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR283; IDB 44796; 9A-9B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        Students at Murray State College, whose names appears elsewhere in this collection.
      - Harold McLean [Herman R. McLean?], Irene Oberhew, Charles Speed (AFS 09748), December 1948, AFC 2004/008: SR284; IDB 44797; 10A-10B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
        McLean and Speed were students at Murray State College; their names appears elsewhere in this collection.
      - Ewing Jackson (AFS 09749), December 1948, January 1949, AFC 2004/008: SR285; IDB 44798; 11A-11B; 1 sound disc: lacquer (aluminum base); analog, 10 in.
    - Sub-subseries 6: New Jersey series J, 1937
      Probably duplicates of originals held by the Archives of Traditional Music, Indiana University
      - Mrs. Lydia Gyderson, AFC 2004/008: SR026; IDB 44209; J1; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Lydia Gyderson, AFC 2004/008: SR027; IDB 44210; J2; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Allen Clevenger, AFC 2004/008: SR028; IDB 44211; J3; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Allen Clevenger; Oliver Minney [?], AFC 2004/008: SR029; IDB 44212; J4; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Harry Grover; Allen Clevenger; Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR030; IDB 44213; J5; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Harry Grover; William Hopkins; Mrs. Frances Asay; Wesley Sheinizer [?]; possibly another person, AFC 2004/008: SR031; IDB 44214; J6; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Bert Reynolds; Howard Johnson, AFC 2004/008: SR032; IDB 44215; J7; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Howard Johnson; Oliver Minney [?], AFC 2004/008: SR033; IDB 44216; J8; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Tom Test [?], AFC 2004/008: SR034; IDB 44229; J9; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Tom Test [?]; Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR035; IDB 44217; J10; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR036; IDB 44218; J11; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Grant, AFC 2004/008: SR037; IDB 44219; J12; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Grant; Bill Thompson, AFC 2004/008: SR038; IDB 44220; J13; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - W.H. Thompson; Jim Pierce, AFC 2004/008: SR039; IDB 44221; J14; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - William Thompson; James Pierce, AFC 2004/008: SR040; IDB 44222; J15; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Jim Pierce; George [no last name given], AFC 2004/008: SR041; IDB 44223; J16; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Charles Parker, AFC 2004/008: SR042; IDB 44224; J17; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Ireland; John Webb, AFC 2004/008: SR043; IDB 44225; J18; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Ireland, AFC 2004/008: SR044; IDB 44226; J19; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Ireland, AFC 2004/008: SR045; IDB 44227; J20; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Ireland, AFC 2004/008: SR046; IDB 44228; J21; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Ireland, AFC 2004/008: SR047; IDB 44230; J22; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - William Ireland; Mrs. Charles Parker, AFC 2004/008: SR048; IDB 44231; J23; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - William Ireland, AFC 2004/008: SR049; IDB 44232; J24; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Mrs. Phoebe Harrison, AFC 2004/008: SR050; IDB 44233; J25; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - John Ireland; Mrs. Lulu Goodenough, AFC 2004/008: SR051; IDB 44234; J26; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.
      - Charles Tilton; Charles Estel [?]; Oliver Minney [?]; Mrs. Lulu Goodenough, AFC 2004/008: SR052; IDB 44235; J27; 1 sound disc: aluminum; analog, 12 in.